They still have their secrets.
The Secret Life of Pets 2 is a family, comedy,
adventure film directed by Chris Renaud.
Max the terrier must cope with some major life changes
when his owner gets married and has a baby.
When the family takes a trip to the countryside, nervous Max has numerous run-ins
with canine-intolerant cows, hostile foxes and a scary turkey.
Luckily for Max, he soon catches a break when he meets Rooster, a gruff
farm dog who tries to cure the lovable pooch of his neuroses.
Max (voice), played by Patton Oswalt.
Snowball (voice), played by Kevin Hart.
Duke (voice), played by Eric Stonestreet.
Gidget (voice), played by Jenny Slate.
Daisy (voice), played by Tiffany Haddish.
Chloe (voice), played by Lake Bell.
The Secret Life of Pets 2 is a 2019 American animated comedy film
directed by Chris Renaud and written by Brian Lynch.
Produced by Illumination, it is the second feature film
in the Secret Life of Pets franchise.
The film features the voices of Patton Oswalt, Eric Stonestreet, Jenny Slate, Kevin Hart, Tiffany Haddish, Lake Bell,
Nick Kroll, Dana Carvey, Ellie Kemper, Renaud, Hannibal Buress, Bobby Moynihan, and Harrison Ford.
The Secret Life of Pets 2 was theatrically released in the United
States on June 7, 2019, by Universal Pictures.
It received mixed reviews from critics, and grossed $431
million against a budget of $80 million.
A further sequel is in development.
The film explores themes of new york city, friendship, villain, sequel, dog.
The tone is lighthearted.